<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<data>
  <row>
    <id>1</id>
    <t>อิกฺตะเราะบะติส สาอฺะตุ วันชักฺกฺ็อล เกฺาะมัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>2</id>
    <t>วะอี ยะเรอ์า อายะตัย ยุอฺ์ริฎู วะยะกฺูลู สิห์รุม มุสตะมิรร์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>3</id>
    <t>วะกัซซะบู วัตตะบะอฺู อะฮ์วาอะฮุม  ^  วะกุลลุ อัมริม มุสตะกฺิรร์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>4</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ญาอะฮุม มินัล อัมบาอิ มา ฟีฮิ มุซดะญัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>5</id>
    <t>ฮิกมะตุม บาลิเฆาะฮ์  ^  ฟะมา ตุฆนิน นุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>6</id>
    <t>ฟะตะวัลละ อฺันฮุม  ^  เยามะ ยัดอฺุด ดาอฺิ อิลา ชัยอิน นุกุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>7</id>
    <t>คุชชะอฺัน อับศอรุฮุม ยัครุญูนะ มินัล อัจญ์ดาษิ กะอันนะฮุม ญะรอดุม มุนตะชิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>8</id>
    <t>มุฮ์ฏิอฺีนะ อิลัด ดาอฺ์  ^  ยะกฺูลุล กาฟิรูนะ ฮาซา เยามุน อฺะสิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>9</id>
    <t>กัซซะบัต กฺ็อบละฮุม เกฺอ์ามุ นูฮิน ฟะกัซซะบู อฺับดะนา วะกฺอลู มัจญ์นูนู วัซดุญิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>10</id>
    <t>ฟะดะอฺา ร็อบบะฮู อันนี มัฆลูบุน ฟันตะศิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>11</id>
    <t>ฟะฟะตะห์นา อับวาบัส สะมาอิ บิมาอิม มุนฮะมิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>12</id>
    <t>วะฟัจญ์ญัรนัล อัรเฎาะ อฺุยูนัน ฟัลตะกฺ็อล มาอุ อฺะลา อัมริน กฺ็อด กฺุดิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>13</id>
    <t>วะฮะมัลนาฮุ อฺะลา ซาติ อัลวาฮิว วะดุสุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>14</id>
    <t>ตัจญ์รี บิอะอฺ์ยุนินา ญะซาอัล ลิมัน กานะ กุฟิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>15</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อต ตะร็อกนาฮา อายะตัน ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>16</id>
    <t>ฟะกัยฟะ กานะ อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>17</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ยัสสัรนัล กฺุรอานะ ลิซซิกริ ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>18</id>
    <t>กัซซะบัต อฺาดุน ฟะกัยฟะ กานะ อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>19</id>
    <t>อินนา อัรสัลนา อฺะลัยฮิม รีฮัน ศ็อรเศาะร็อน ฟี เยามิ นะห์สิม มุสตะมิรร์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>20</id>
    <t>ตันซิอฺุน นาสะ กะอันนะฮุม อะอฺ์ญาซุ นัคลิม มุนเกฺาะอฺิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>21</id>
    <t>ฟะกัยฟะ กานะ อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>22</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ยัสสัรนัล กฺุรอานะ ลิซซิกริ ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>23</id>
    <t>กัซซะบัต ษะมูดุ บินนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>24</id>
    <t>ฟะกฺอลู อะบะชะร็อม มินนา วาฮิดัน นัตตะบิอฺุฮู อินนา อิซัล ละฟี เฎาะลาลิว วะสุอฺุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>25</id>
    <t>อะอุลกฺิยัซ ซิกรุ อฺะลัยฮิ มิม บัยนินา บัล ฮุวะ กัซซาบุน อะชิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>26</id>
    <t>สะยะอฺ์ละมูนะ เฆาะดัม มะนิล กัซซาบุล อะชิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>27</id>
    <t>อินนา มุรสิลุน นาเกฺาะติ ฟิตนะตัล ละฮุม ฟัรตะกฺิบฮุม วัศเฏาะบิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>28</id>
    <t>วะนับบิอ์ฮุม อันนัล มาอะ กฺิสมะตุม บัยนะฮุม  ^  กุลลุ ชิรบิม มุห์ตะฎ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>29</id>
    <t>ฟะนาเดา ศอฮิบะฮุม ฟะตะอฺาฏอ ฟะอฺะกฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>30</id>
    <t>ฟะกัยฟะ กานะ อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>31</id>
    <t>อินนา อัรสัลนา อฺะลัยฮิม ศ็อยฮะเตา วาฮิดะตัน ฟะกานู กะฮะชีมิล มุห์ตะซฺิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>32</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ยัสสัรนัล กฺุรอานะ ลิซซิกริ ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>33</id>
    <t>กัซซะบัต เกฺอ์ามุ ลูฏิม บินนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>34</id>
    <t>อินนา อัรสัลนา อฺะลัยฮิม ฮาศิบัน อิลลา อาละ ลูฏ  ^  นัจญ์ญัยนาฮุม บิสะฮัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>35</id>
    <t>นิอฺ์มะตัม มิน อฺินดินา  ^  กะซาลิกะ นัจญ์ซี มัน ชะกัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>36</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด อันซะเราะฮุม บัฏชะตะนา ฟะตะมาเรอ์า บินนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>37</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด รอวะดูฮุ อฺัน ฎ็อยฟิฮี ฟะเฏาะมัสนา อะอฺ์ยุนะฮุม ฟะซูกฺู อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>38</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ศ็อบบะฮะฮุม บุกเราะตัน อฺะซาบุม มุสตะกฺิรร์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>39</id>
    <t>ฟะซูกฺู อฺะซาบี วะนุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>40</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ยัสสัรนัล กฺุรอานะ ลิซซิกริ ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>41</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด ญาอะ อาละ ฟิรเอฺานัน นุซุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>42</id>
    <t>กัซซะบู บิอายาตินา กุลลิฮา ฟะอะค็อซนาฮุม อัคซะ อฺะซีซิม มุกฺตะดิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>43</id>
    <t>อะกุฟฟารุกุม ค็อยรุม มิน อุลาอิกุม อัม ละกุม บะรออะตุน ฟิซ ซุบุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>44</id>
    <t>อัม ยะกฺูลูนะ นะห์นุ ญะมีอฺุม มุนตะศิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>45</id>
    <t>สะยุฮ์ซะมุล ญัมอฺุ วะยุวัลลูนัด ดุบุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>46</id>
    <t>บะลิส สาอฺะตุ เมาอฺิดุฮุม วัสสาอฺะตุ อัดฮา วะอะมัรร์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>47</id>
    <t>อินนัล มุจญ์ริมีนะ ฟี เฎาะลาลิว วะสุอฺุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>48</id>
    <t>เยามะ ยุสฮะบูนะ ฟิน นาริ อฺะลา วุญูฮิฮิม ซูกฺู มัสสะ สะกฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>49</id>
    <t>อินนา กุลละ ชัยอิน เคาะลักฺนาฮุ บิเกฺาะดัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>50</id>
    <t>วะมา อัมรุนา อิลลา วาฮิดะตุน กะลัมฮิม บิลบะศ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>51</id>
    <t>วะละกฺ็อด อะฮ์ลักนา อัชยาอฺะกุม ฟะฮัล มิม มุดดะกิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>52</id>
    <t>วะกุลลุ ชัยอิน ฟะอฺะลูฮุ ฟิซ ซุบุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>53</id>
    <t>วะกุลลุ เศาะฆีริว วะกะบีริม มุสตะฏ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>54</id>
    <t>อินนัล มุตตะกฺีนะ ฟี ญันนาติว วะนะฮัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>55</id>
    <t>ฟี มักฺอฺะดิ ศิดกฺิน อฺินดะ มะลีกิม มุกฺตะดิร</t>
  </row>
</data>
