<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<data>
  <row>
    <id>1</id>
    <t>ยาอัยยุฮัล มุซซัมมิล</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>2</id>
    <t>กฺุมิล ลัยละ อิลลา เกฺาะลีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>3</id>
    <t>นิศฟะฮู อะวิน กฺุศ มินฮุ เกฺาะลีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>4</id>
    <t>เอา ซิด อฺะลัยฮิ วะร็อตติลิล กฺุรอานะ ตัรตีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>5</id>
    <t>อินนา สะนุลกฺี อฺะลัยกะ เกฺอ์าลัน ษะกฺีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>6</id>
    <t>อินนะ นาชิอะตัล ลัยลิ ฮิยะ อะชัดดุ วัฏเอา วะอักฺวะมุ กฺีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>7</id>
    <t>อินนะ ละกะ ฟิน นะฮาริ สับฮัน เฏาะวีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>8</id>
    <t>วัซกุริส มะ ร็อบบิกะ วะตะบัตตัล อิลัยฮิ ตับตีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>9</id>
    <t>ร็อบบุล มัชริกฺิ วัลมัฆริบิ ลา อิลาฮะ อิลลา ฮุวะ ฟัตตะคิซฮุ วะกีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>10</id>
    <t>วัศบิร อฺะลา มา ยะกฺูลูนะ วะฮ์ญุรฮุม ฮัจญ์ร็อน ญะมีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>11</id>
    <t>วะซัรนี วัลมุกัซซิบีนะ อุลิน นะอฺ์มะติ วะมะฮ์ฮิลฮุม เกฺาะลีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>12</id>
    <t>อินนะ ละดัยนา อันกาเลา วะญะฮีมา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>13</id>
    <t>วะเฏาะอฺามัน ซา ฆุศเศาะติว วะอฺะซาบัน อะลีมา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>14</id>
    <t>เยามะ ตัรญุฟุล อัรฎุ วัลญิบาลุ วะกานะติล ญิบาลุ กะษีบัม มะฮีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>15</id>
    <t>อินนา อัรสัลนา อิลัยกุม เราะสูลัน ชาฮิดัน อฺะลัยกุม กะมา อัรสัลนา อิลา ฟิรเอฺานะ เราะสูลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>16</id>
    <t>ฟะอฺะศอ ฟิรเอฺานุร เราะสูละ ฟะอะค็อซนาฮุ อัคเซา วะบีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>17</id>
    <t>ฟะกัยฟะ ตัตตะกฺูนะ อิน กะฟัรตุม เยามัย ยัจญ์อฺะลุล วิลดานะ ชีบา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>18</id>
    <t>อัสสะมาอุ มุนฟะฏิรุม บิฮ์  ^  กานะ วะอฺ์ดุฮู มัฟอฺูลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>19</id>
    <t>อินนะ ฮาซิฮี ตัซกิเราะฮ์  ^  ฟะมัน ชาอัต ตะเคาะซะ อิลา ร็อบบิฮี สะบีลา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>20</id>
    <t>อินนะ ร็อบบะกะ ยะอฺ์ละมุ อันนะกะ ตะกฺูมุ อัดนา มิน ษุลุษะยิล ลัยลิ วะนิศฟะฮู วะษุลุษะฮู วะฏออิฟะตุม มินัล ละซีนะ มะอฺัก  ^  วัลลอฮุ ยุกฺ็อดดิรุล ลัยละ วันนะฮาร  ^  อฺะลิมะ อัล ลัน ตุห์ศูฮุ ฟะตาบะ อฺะลัยกุม  ^  ฟักฺเราะอู มา ตะยัสสะเราะ มินัล กฺุรอาน  ^  อฺะลิมะ อัน สะยะกูนุ มินกุม มัรฎอ วะอาเคาะรูนะ ยัฎริบูนะ ฟิล อัรฎิ ยับตะฆูนะ มิน ฟัฎลิล ลาฮิ วะอาเคาะรูนะ ยุกฺอติลูนะ ฟี สะบีลิล ลาฮ์  ^  ฟักฺเราะอู มา ตะยัสสะเราะ มินฮ์  ^  วะอะกฺีมุศ เศาะลาตะ วะอาตุซ ซะกาตะ วะอักฺริฎุล ลอฮะ กฺ็อรฎ็อน ฮะสะนา  ^  วะมา ตุกฺ็อดดิมู ลิอันฟุสิกุม มิน ค็อยริน ตะญิดูฮุ อฺินดัล ลอฮิ ฮุวะ ค็อยเรอ์า วะอะอฺ์เซฺาะมะ อัจญ์รอ  ^  วัสตัฆฟิรุล ลอฮ์  ^  อินนัล ลอฮะ เฆาะฟูรุร เราะฮีม</t>
  </row>
</data>
