<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<data>
  <row>
    <id>1</id>
    <t>ยาอัยยุฮัล มุดดัษษิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>2</id>
    <t>กฺุม ฟะอันซิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>3</id>
    <t>วะร็อบบะกะ ฟะกับบิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>4</id>
    <t>วะษิยาบะกะ ฟะเฏาะฮ์ฮิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>5</id>
    <t>วัรรุจญ์ซะ ฟะฮ์ญุร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>6</id>
    <t>วะลา ตัมนุน ตัสตักษิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>7</id>
    <t>วะลิร็อบบิกะ ฟัศบิร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>8</id>
    <t>ฟะอิซา นุกฺิเราะ ฟิน นากฺูร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>9</id>
    <t>ฟะซาลิกะ เยามะอิซี เยามุน อฺะสีร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>10</id>
    <t>อฺะลัล กาฟิรีนะ ฆ็อยรุ ยะสีร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>11</id>
    <t>ซัรนี วะมัน เคาะลักฺตุ วะฮีดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>12</id>
    <t>วะญะอฺัลตุ ละฮู มาลัม มัมดูดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>13</id>
    <t>วะบะนีนะ ชุฮูดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>14</id>
    <t>วะมะฮ์ฮัตตุ ละฮู ตัมฮีดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>15</id>
    <t>ษุมมะ ยัฏมะอฺุ อัน อะซีด</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>16</id>
    <t>กัลลา  ^  อินนะฮู กานะ ลิอายาตินา อฺะนีดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>17</id>
    <t>สะอุรฮิกฺุฮู เศาะอฺูดา</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>18</id>
    <t>อินนะฮู ฟักกะเราะ วะกฺ็อดดัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>19</id>
    <t>ฟะกฺุติละ กัยฟะ กฺ็อดดัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>20</id>
    <t>ษุมมะ กฺุติละ กัยฟะ กฺ็อดดัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>21</id>
    <t>ษุมมะ นะซฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>22</id>
    <t>ษุมมะ อฺะบะสะ วะบะสัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>23</id>
    <t>ษุมมะ อัดบะเราะ วัสตักบัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>24</id>
    <t>ฟะกฺอละ อิน ฮาซา อิลลา สิห์รุย ยุอ์ษัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>25</id>
    <t>อิน ฮาซา อิลลา เกฺอ์าลุล บะชัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>26</id>
    <t>สะอุศลีฮิ สะกฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>27</id>
    <t>วะมา อัดรอกะ มา สะกฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>28</id>
    <t>ลา ตุบกฺี วะลา ตะซัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>29</id>
    <t>เลาวาฮะตุล ลิลบะชัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>30</id>
    <t>อฺะลัยฮา ติสอฺะตะ อฺะชัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>31</id>
    <t>วะมา ญะอฺัลนา อัศฮาบัน นาริ อิลลา มะลาอิกะฮ์  ^  วะมา ญะอฺัลนา อฺิดดะตะฮุม อิลลา ฟิตนะตัล ลิลละซีนะ กะฟะรู ลิยัสตัยกฺินัล ละซีนะ อูตุล กิตาบะ วะยัซดาดัล ละซีนะ อามะนู อีมาเนา วะลา ยัรตาบัล ละซีนะ อูตุล กิตาบะ วัลมุอ์มินูนะ วะลิยะกฺูลัล ละซีนะ ฟี กฺุลูบิฮิม มะเราะฎู วัลกาฟิรูนะ มาซา อะรอดัล ลอฮุ บิฮาซา มะษะลา  ^  กะซาลิกะ ยุฎิลลุล ลอฮุ มัย ยะชาอุ วะยะฮ์ดี มัย ยะชาอ์  ^  วะมา ยะอฺ์ละมุ ญุนูดะ ร็อบบิกะ อิลลา ฮู  ^  วะมา ฮิยะ อิลลา ซิกรอ ลิลบะชัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>32</id>
    <t>กัลลา วัลเกฺาะมัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>33</id>
    <t>วัลลัยลิ อิซ อัดบัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>34</id>
    <t>วัศศุบฮิ อิซา อัสฟัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>35</id>
    <t>อินนะฮา ละอิห์ดัล กุบัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>36</id>
    <t>นะซีร็อล ลิลบะชัร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>37</id>
    <t>ลิมัน ชาอะ มินกุม อัย ยะตะกฺ็อดดะมะ เอา ยะตะอัคค็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>38</id>
    <t>กุลลุ นัฟสิม บิมา กะสะบัต เราะฮีนะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>39</id>
    <t>อิลลา อัศฮาบัล ยะมีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>40</id>
    <t>ฟี ญันนาตี ยะตะสาอะลูน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>41</id>
    <t>อฺะนิล มุจญ์ริมีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>42</id>
    <t>มา สะละกะกุม ฟี สะกฺ็อร</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>43</id>
    <t>กฺอลู ลัม นะกุ มินัล มุศ็อลลีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>44</id>
    <t>วะลัม นะกุ นุฏอฺิมุล มิสกีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>45</id>
    <t>วะกุนนา นะคูฎุ มะอฺัล คออิฎีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>46</id>
    <t>วะกุนนา นุกัซซิบุ บิเยามิด ดีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>47</id>
    <t>ฮัตตา อะตานัล ยะกฺีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>48</id>
    <t>ฟะมา ตันฟะอฺุฮุม ชะฟาอฺะตุช ชาฟิอฺีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>49</id>
    <t>ฟะมา ละฮุม อฺะนิต ตัซกิเราะติ มุอฺ์ริฎีน</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>50</id>
    <t>กะอันนะฮุม ฮุมุรุม มุสตันฟิเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>51</id>
    <t>ฟัรร็อต มิน กฺ็อสวะเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>52</id>
    <t>บัล ยุรีดุ กุลลุม รีอิม มินฮุม อัย ยุอ์ตา ศุฮุฟัม มุนัชชะเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>53</id>
    <t>กัลลา  ^  บัล ลา ยะคอฟูนัล อาคิเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>54</id>
    <t>กัลลา อินนะฮู ตัซกิเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>55</id>
    <t>ฟะมัน ชาอะ ซะกะเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
  <row>
    <id>56</id>
    <t>วะมา ยัซกุรูนะ อิลลา อัย ยะชาอัล ลอฮ์  ^  ฮุวะ อะฮ์ลุต ตักฺวา วะอะฮ์ลุล มัฆฟิเราะฮ์</t>
  </row>
</data>
